Ahh, I cannot believe you guys
aren't gonna play with these.
We told you, you don't. It's mint-in-box.
l don't know. I just think it's a waste.
Just relax, I'm just looking at the box.
(Sheldon:)You should look with your eyes and not
your muscular Nebraska man-hands.
(Penny:)What is your problem?
(Sheldon:)My problem is that I don't want you
to break Leonard's toy...
(Sheldon:)...which you probably did by shaking it.
She shook it, we all saw her.
(Penny:)Leonard, I bought you this
because I wanted you to have fun with it.
l didn't want it to sit in this box.
You know what? You're right.
l mean, it's from you.
I'm never gonna sell it.
(Leonard:)- I'm opening it.
- Yes.
(Sheldon:)- It's broken.
- What?